

SAIFUDDIN ANSARI

Mm hall Saifi hostel Aligarh Muslim University Amu Aligarh ,202002 (8077677472),(9045709068) saifuddinansari92@gmail.com

😚 https://www.redbubble.com/people/saif0786/shop?asc=u

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/saifuddin-ansari-b5a71b1a1

f https://www.facebook.com/saifuddin.ansari.969

OBJECTIVE

Elementary education teacher looking for a position at art & craft college, institutions, school.where I can apply my 2 years of teaching experience in College periods side work with NGO organization team and my curriculum development skills.

SKILLS

Assistant Professor Fine Arts

Art & Craft & painting teacher.

Digital graphics artist

Sketch artist, On spot painting demonstration

LANGUAGE

English , Hindi, Urdu

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

3rd position in North zone Youth festival Painting competition -2016 Punjab agricultural University, Ludhiana.

2nd position in North zone Painting competition-2017 C.S.J.M.U kanpur.

3rd position in National painting competition - 2017 All india inter University national youth festival Shivaji University ,Kolhapur.

Youth festival 2nd position State level painting Competition MJP Rohil khand University Barely ,UP

1st prices in Art niche Painting competition University fine arts club Cultural education center ,amu

Achievement Gold medalist Annual hall function Mohsinul mulk hall ,2017

Merit award aligarh Muslim University Sir Syed award On spot painting 2015

EXPERIENCE

Manuu cte BHOPAL

11/3/2021 - Non

Assistant Professor (contractual)

Assistant Professor, Fine Arts.

Teaching B.ed 3rd sem.

Maulana Azad National Urdu University

Virasat ngo

2017 - 2019

As an artist school field work

Demonstration of art and craft in workshop
organised by virasat ngo.at Ayesha Tarin
modern public school & different school places
in Aligarh

E learning college

2021 - 2021

Teaching assistant

E-learning online College

Teaching assistant

Certificate

National skil development corporation (skill India)

2021 - 2021

Domestic data entry operator Skill India , domestic data entry operator Certificate

International watercolour society Biennale (Pakistan)

2020 - 2020

IWS

Participation in international watercolour society Biennale pakistan (2020)

Fine arts club CEC

2018 - 2018

Art Niche

Fine arts club CEC,

Art Niche exhibition

And demonstration as an artist

ACTIVITIES

Watching documentary ,on spot painting Photography

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of

: 12/03/1992

Birth

Marital

: Single

Status

Nationality: Indian

As an artist

: Indian visual artist ,Art & Craft teacher,

illustrater and Sketch artist & digital.

Prismania an art Exhibition

2018 - 2018

Exhibition

Prismania an art Exhibition

Moinuddin Ahmed art gallery

Aligarh, amu

German art gallery

2020 - 2020

Virtual art exhibition

'Sound of silence' a virtual art exhibition

By international German art gallery

IG khan memorial trust

2015 - 2018

Installation art

IG khan memorial trust under work

3 year installation and photography work

Kochi biennale

2016 - 2017

Installation art

Kochi muzrish Biennale international Biennale in india organized by kochi Biennale work at installation theme based work

EDUCATION

E learning college

2021

Teaching assistant certificate

1st

E-learning college

2021

Fashion designing (short course)

1st

Aligarh Muslim University

2018-2020

Master of fine arts (MFA)

840 grade, 1st division

Aligarh Muslim University

2014-2018

Bachelor of Fine arts (BFA)

1st division 75%

BSEB Patna

2009

High school

315 1st division

PUBLICATION

Annual hall book cover design

Annual hall function book published front cover page painting design with reference artist